Shannon Hawley

Accounts Payable Specialist

Corona, CA 92881 shannonmiller96_xgw@indeedemail.com 949-929-5530

A highly motivated Accounts Receivable, and Accounts Payable professional with a verifiable record of accomplishment spanning ten years. Highly creative, recognized as a results-oriented and solution-focused individual. Areas of strength include:

- · Accounts Payable
- Organizational Skills
- Computer Literate
- Work as Team Player
- Heavy Phones
- Accounts Receivable
- Batching and Coding
- Communication Skills via phone and email
- Time Management Skills
- Research Abilities
- Customer Service
- Organization of files for year end 1099's

#readytowork

Work Experience

Accounts Payable Specialist

Complete Business Systems for Accountemps - Upland, CA January 2020 to March 2020

Full cycle accounts payable. I processed the AP for 5 companies. Two with locations in California and 3 with locations in Reno Nevada. I would receive invoices via mail and email and would process daily. I also reconciled multiple company credit cards and gas cards. With receipts and employee expense reports. I also set up new files for year 2020. Worked closely with vendors in payment status and or missing invoices.

Accounts Payable Processor

Advantex Professional Services - Fullerton, CA November 2019 to November 2019

Processed 50+ invoices daily. Accrued sales try as when necessary. Created processed batches daily for approval for payment in the weekly check run.

Accounts Payable Specialist

Randstad Professionals - Costa Mesa, CA September 2015 to May 2019

Hoag Hospital Presbyterian

Full cycle accounts payable, I handled Letter A, and the drop ship invoices for Hoag, Irvine (Hoag), and Hoag Orthopedic on the alphabet. I also handled the expenses for Hoag imaging and month end accruals. I worked daily with P.O. and non purchase order invoices. Non po invoices, non po invoices were sent to department coordinators for the appropriate approval and or to the buyers for the po # if there should be one. The cut off each week was Monday's at 12 pm for non po invoices. The cut off for all invoices to be entered in the system for that week's check run was Thursday at 3 pm. Any checks over \$100k were given to the CFO for additional signature. Checks were matched to back up which was filed weekly. If there were discrepancies with purchase order and invoice. I would coordinate with the purchasing group or the vendor depending on the situation. Purchase order invoices were 3 way matched (invoice, packing slip, and PO) before entered into the system. Handled inquires via email, or phone for payment status. Missing invoices or other inquiries.

Accounts Payable Specialist

Identified Talent Solutions - Irvine, CA June 2015 to August 2015

Endologix

Full cycle accounts payable, I handled M - Z on the alphabet. I worked daily with P.O. and non purchase order invoices. Once received would separate po from non po invoices, non po invoices were sent to department coordinators for the appropriate approval. The cut off each week was Tuesday's at 2 pm. For invoices to be entered in the system for that week's check run. Were we would run the open bills report, get approval from the finance manager, as well as the budget select the open bills for payment up to the weekly budget amount, once checks were run they were given to the controller to sign off. Any checks over \$10k were given to the CFO for additional signature. Checks were matched to back up which was filed weekly. Of there were discrepancies with purchase order invoices I would coordinate with the purchasing group or the vendor depending on the situation. Purchase order invoices were 3 way matched (invoice, packing slip, and PO) before entered into the system. Handled inquires via email, or phone for payment status. Missing invoices or other inquiries. Set up new suppliers as needed.

Accounts Receivable Clerk

Irvine Technology Corp - Irvine, CA February 2015 to May 2015

Stratacare

Assist AR with printing and saving to AR excel workbooks daily payment transfers for several clients. Saving client payment email as CVS and excel workbook and doing pivot table. Assist AR with scanning copying, and doing cover sheet for payments received to be sent to Xerox. Assist AR with the research of unapplied cash, the allocation of unapplied cash (ex by doing pivot tables) as well as the offset worksheets for unapplied cash.

Accounts Payable Clerk

Ledgent Agency - Costa Mesa, CA December 2014 to December 2014

Sampling International

Accounts payable getting daily mail. Answering incoming calls and transferring to appropriate person or taking messages as necessary. Coding and posting of invoices into MYOB, researching and resolving issues with invoices (wrong amount approved, not our invoice), reconciliation of credit card statements matching receipts. Getting appropriate signature and mailing of payments.

Accounts Payable Clerk

AppleOne Agency - Newport Beach, CA May 2014 to October 2014

Renovo Solutions

Full Cycle accounts payable, opening daily mail (approximately 1500+ invoices weekly), batching and uploading invoice into purchase order system. Coding and posting of invoices into QuickBooks, researching and resolving issues with invoices (wrong purchase order#, wrong amount approved, not our invoice), and selection of invoices and cutting of checks for weekly check run. Getting appropriate signature and mailing of payments.

Bookkeeper

Randstad Agency - Irvine, CA February 2014 to March 2014

Sares Regis

Downloading of invoices from outside source and importing to JD Edwards software, downloading and processing of high volume 2000+ invoices weekly, verifying approval, and accuracy of invoices, research and resolve problems with property managers. Getting VP or higher approval for anything over \$25,000, verifying and cutting of checks weekly mailing them out.

Accounts Payable Clerk

Apria Healthcare February 2011 to December 2013

Accounts Payable

Processing batching and coding of Travel and Expense reports for Apria and Coram employees approximately 200 per week; data entry in both Lawson and JD Edwards's systems for month end close. Processing of online mileage for Apria employees, coding and batching of utility and phone bills for Apria and Praxair approximately 1500+ invoices a week. Started this position as a temporary employee.

Medical Bill Review Analyst

ACS Comp IQ A Xerox Company - Santa Ana, CA March 2010 to February 2011

Workers Comp

Coding and processing of workers compensation related medical bills according to individual state fee schedules, state and federal regulations in a timely manner. Have the ability to process up to 65 - 120 bills with at least 98% accuracy, meet deadlines, while working in a fast paced team work environment.

Accounts Receivable Associate II

Beech Street A Viant Network April 2007 to February 2009

Lake Forrest, CA Health Insurance

Processing of all accounts receivable for Beech Street (Viant) Finance Dept; processing of daily lock boxes and reports, in conjunction with team members, coding, matching of backup to invoices; processing of daily wire transfers, corroboration with collections team regarding discrepancies, posting

of cash to current and past invoices, refunds, and answering client's questions, month end procedures, and balancing; and begin procedures for the next month's opening.

Education

Diploma in Medical Billing and Coding

Career Networks Institute - Orange, CA September 2009 to June 2010

High school or equivalent in General

Savanna High School - Anaheim, CA September 1995 to June 1996

Skills

- Accounting
- · Quick books
- Jd edwards (9 years)
- Lawson (4 years)
- Oracle
- Ariba (2 years)
- Microsoft excel (9 years)
- Powerpoint
- Microsoft word (9 years)
- Word perfect
- · Point of sale
- Accounts Payable (10+ years)
- Accounts Receivable (2 years)
- Quickbooks (3 years)
- Google Docs (Less than 1 year)
- · Accounting Software
- Office Management

Assessments

Accounting Skills: Bookkeeping — Highly Proficient

February 2019

Measures a candidate's ability to calculate and determine the accuracy of financial data. Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share assignment/yojxi1i-nk-rkiof

Accounting: Basic Principles — Familiar

September 2019

Preparing financial records according to federal policies.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share_to_profile/

fa8dc80fcee46d4d2716b74292851380eed53dc074545cb7

Office Manager — Familiar

October 2019

Scheduling and budgeting.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share_to_profile/

e2f359794229a82e8a1e65c24572db87eed53dc074545cb7

Attention to Detail — Highly Proficient

December 2019

Identifying differences in materials, following instructions, and detecting details among distracting information.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

share to profile/276b7c06a33e4791fa955c4e404a5d09eed53dc074545cb7

Accounting Skills: Bookkeeping — Familiar

May 2020

Calculating and determining the accuracy of financial data.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share to profile/

ffa73cb9ac30b83b15c<u>63761eb5691e4eed53dc074545cb7</u>

Verbal Communication — Proficient

May 2020

Speaking clearly, correctly, and concisely.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share to profile/

a0ad6a5d9ddeb413f2ac70f880d9f694eed53dc074545cb7

Data Entry — Highly Proficient

May 2020

Entering data quickly and accurately.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

share to profile/2d65adc03df5188c0e2c6d3d9eff6aa0eed53dc074545cb7

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.

Additional Information

COMPUTER SKILLS

IBM and Mac Literate, Word Perfect, Microsoft Word, PowerPoint

Microsoft Excel, Barcc, Heat Self Service, Beacon. Content Manager, Ariba (All Database Software) Extra Software, Quicken, Quick Books & Quick Books Point of Sale, Oracle Software, JD Edwards, Lawson, MYOB, and Nav (All Accounting Software)